LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now. Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may swallow you, flying in glory
Thank you for giving me a heart.
Done!
The
Fortunate
Ones
Oh...
It's you.
You surprised me.
You don't usually call me at this time of day.
You shouldn't talk...
You never hang out with us anymore.
So, what is it?
Mmm, something is bothering me a little...
That girl over there got a
heart transplant last month.
Her parents were overjoyed that
a compatible heart was found.
They apparently wanted to
thank the donor in person.
It seems like a happy story to this point.
Yes...
The heart donor is a boy that is under my care;
he had to replace some parts of his body
with cybernetic implants for treatment,
and he got a cybernetic heart, since the implants
would have overburdened his biological heart,
but his parents are saying that they
don't remember donating the organ at all.
They could be compulsive liars, or just shy;
there could be errors in
coordinating the transplant,
or post-factum memory confusion...
Any other possible aftereffects?
The boy's mother apparently
went to consult the police,
but the detective in charge got into an accident,
so the investigation is currently stalled.
I don't know if this is your territory,
but... it just bothers me...
The surgery was necessitated by a
sudden accident and had to be rushed,
and it seems that they were prepared to give her a full
cybernetic body if an organ hadn't become available.
Since she is so young,
she would have had to periodically switch to
new cybernetic bodies as she aged,
which would have been stressful,
not to mention all the costs and maintenance
it would have involved; she was quite lucky.
How old is she?
She is still only six years old.
So, the information wasn't anything significant.
What now? Should we just go back?
Go to the company that supposedly
coordinated her transplant, Meditech.
I'll have Ishikawa and Boma check
the cash flow before they join you.
Something on your mind?
You know that there have been mass abductions
here involving overseas mafias recently, right?
Those involved in the black market trade
of organs and cybernetic devices, you mean?
It's possible that domestic channels
aiding the smugglers are involved in this case too.
I want to investigate this.
Understood.
Roger.
Sorry to have kept you waiting;
allow me to introduce the CEO of
Meditech, Mr. Iwasaki.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Togusa from Public Safety's Section 9.
Oh, I'm a secretary android; Mr. Iwasaki is here.
Oh, well...
Oh, please, don't feel bad about it.
It happens all the time.
People just don't seem to recognise
Jameson type cyborgs for some reason.
My kids always scold me about having
a bad taste in cyborg bodies, too.
Still, it's about my principles,
and they cannot be compromised, so...
Oh, oops... sorry about that.
So, I heard you wanted to confirm something?
JAPAN'S #1
Please.
Okay.
It's about this...
All right, let's see...
Hmm, it is indeed our invoice slip...
Niihama General Hospital
But, strangely...
Coordinating transplants is not
one of our company's services.
Well, if you want to look over anything, go ahead.
If I remember correctly,
your company advertises for people to register
their genomes with you so that spare
organs can be manufactured on demand.
Oh, yes.
We splice our customer's
genetic information into pigs
and "grow" the desired organs.
When required,
we can extract the organ and deliver it.
Is it lucrative?
Why are you asking? Of course it is!
You should register your genome
and reserve an organ pig, too.
Our basic plan includes registration
for five different organs;
if you sign up now, I'll give you a special deal.
Make your pitch to him; his body is still flesh.
Well, I'm not particularly....
Oh, what a shame.
If you don't require the organs
during the pig's lifetime,
just sell them to existing
transplant coordination companies.
If you're going to invest in this field,
invest in Meditech!
And while we're talking about investing, there's
no reason Ms Cyborg here shouldn't invest as well!
Well then, do what you want.
If there are any questions, please call me.
Thank you.
I guess he's the folksy type that you'll
find no matter what era you live in.
You mean to say that he's
the "Osaka Merchant" type?
What a stereotype.
He's taking pains to speak in a bad Kansai
dialect to present himself that way, that's all.
Still, to think that the CEO of the largest
company in the artificial organ industry
Is a cyborg that's using a Jameson-type body...
Considering his enthusiasm,
I wonder if he sold his own organs.
And that's why he's in that box?
It's not too far-fetched of an idea.
Yo.
We're here to take over...
Good job.
We found something when we
looked into the cash flow.
An amount of money from the Crime Victim's
Compensation Fund is being paid to this company.
This one.
However, there is no record
of the transaction here,
and there is no corresponding evidence in either
its communications or operational records.
Falsification of data from the outside, perhaps?
That's probably it.
Even though Meditech's a huge company,
their internal data is so badly protected
it can leak like water through a sieve.
Togusa, let's go see the hospitalized
detective in charge of the investigation.
Do a good job!
I believe it happened last weekend...
He collapsed while conducting an
investigation; the hospitalization was sudden.
Test results came up positive for drugs,
and while faint,
there are also signs of memory confusion.
Hmm?
Hey!
Are you all right?
Damn it, they got him!
Major!
Get in and be quick about it.
Sorry!
I'll hear your excuses later.
Tachikoma, you there?
On the hospital rooftop!
Don't be late!
That was close.
I was starting to get worried because
you guys were late coming out.
What are you saying?
It was because you got greedy in the
first place that we forgot to switch a label!
We erased that detective's memory,
so we're fine now, aren't we?
In any case, I wonder who that guy was just now.
How would I know?
His co-worker or something, I bet.
Tachikoma, do you think you
can overtake the vehicle?
I can get onto it,
but that'd be pretty noticeable.
Keep following us from above;
confirm the vehicle's licence plate.
Roger!
Togusa, stay on standby and keep monitoring
the Omni-directional wireless com system.
We're going to scatter a probe virus,
so you can determine the echo factor.
What?
Wouldn't that violate the
Radio Communications Law?
It's what we call a localized state of emergency.
Roger.
When we exit this tunnel,
we can transmit the virus.
Transmission standby, okay.
Go!
We got it.
Determined the escaping vehicle;
also confirmed its registered user.
It seems that the fugitive is
a medical student in residency.
What do you want to do?
They intend to go to the port's
warehouse district and to hide.
It's about time to call Batou.
Continue to chase the escaping vehicle.
I will meet up with Batou in the Tachikoma.
Roger.
We took it too far.
Doing more would be too dangerous!
Let's hurry up and toss these out!
We were only providing organs at cut-throat prices
to citizens who couldn't get cybernetic
implants for various reasons.
Besides, even if we get caught,
my dad will take care of it, somehow.
Still, for now, what should we do with these?
We'll hide them, along with the
car, until the dust settles.
There are tons of warehouses
and junkyards up ahead.
No one will notice one car abandoned there.
I'm worried about that guy.
He suddenly shot at us, too.
What if he's one of the overseas mafia
who've been conducting mass abductions?
No way.
No, that's it!
It's because we moved in on their territory!
If they catch us, won't hey hack
us apart and sell the parts?!
if they're the mafia, they'll do it...
We're finished!
We're in big trouble...!
Hey, shut up for a second, will you?
TRANSMISSION
BLOCKED
Then, it IS true!
We might... really be in trouble.
Batou, can you hear me?
I can also see you.
I'm waiting at the rendezvous, as ordered.
We're going to corner the
subject vehicle at point D-3.
Feel free to terrorise them, without killing them.
Hey hey, are you sure we
can do something that fun?
I don't care.
Ha, that's the way things should be.
Tachikoma!
All righty!
Oh, that's the car.
Don't hit anyone, okay?
Leave it to me!
I rock!
Hurry up and get out of the car!
We're going to run!
Oooh, they're putting up a good fight.
All right, now for the second round.
Well then, without restraint...
Yo! I put on a real show for them, just like you wanted.
Good job.
H, hey... isn't this going a bit far?
P, please forgive us!
Student ID
Class of '32
Niihama Dental School
Medical Nanotechnology
Manufacturing Department
As we thought, a med student, huh.
It makes me depressed to think that guys like
these could be messing around inside my head.
Batou-San!
Look at what I found!
To sum up the situation,
You were changing labels, without permission, and extracted
organs that had been exchanged with cybernetic implants,
and were selling them, right?
There should be one more.
Oh? He's a tough one.
I'll go get him.
No.
Leave it to me.
The scam seems too vicious for something that
was just supposed to earn them pocket money.
This affair will only be swept under
the rug if we let the law deal with it.
I'll go give him a good "lesson".
Wooo, scary.
Did something happen?
Who knows.
Listen up.
You guys will be dealt with by me.
Hhhhhelp us, pplease ddon't take our organs.
Huh?
I'm sure anyone who sees your face
would think that you're in the mafia.
H, hey! Me too?
Wh, what is that?
Wh, what the hell is it?
I win!
From what I see, you have no cybernetic implants.
I'm sure you'd fetch a high price if I
sold you piecemeal on the black market.
H, hey, wait a minute.
I have good connections!
It's good business, want to team up?
If I ask my dad,
we can have cars and warehouses, too.
We wouldn't have trouble getting funds, either.
It's not a bad deal, don't you think?
Did you think we'd negotiate with peons like you?
We'll take your connections and
silence you for the hell of it.
If we spread your organs around on the market, there
will be no evidence and we'd also make a profit.
We'll kill two birds with one stone.
W, wait, please!
O, ok, I got it!
Is it money?
If it's about money,
my dad will give you however much you want.
R, right? How much do you want?
Your game has gone too far.
You've stuck your neck out in a
world where there's no turning back.
P, please, forgive me!
I won't do it again!
I beg of you! I won't do it again!
Please! Let me go!
Too bad.
They won't let you off this easy.
There are many in the underground who
have no interest in listening to reason.
Clean up your act while you still can.
You have money and schooling;
you're healthy on top of that, aren't you?
Major! I can't... get... out!
We'll come pick you up later; stay put.
We're going to hand these guys over to the police.
Okay!
Oh, it's Batou-San!
Oh, hey man.
Hey, wasn't the Major a bit strange today?
Uh, well, the Major seemed a
bit different today, that's all.
Well. the Major became a complete cyborg
when she was around that girl's age.
I'm sure she had some issues with this case.
Hmm.
Still have something on your mind?
No, nothing really.
Just thinking that, in this world,
there are those, like that girl,
who have no choice but
to undergo an organ transplant,
as well as those like that CEO who voluntarily
sell their organs to become a cyborg.
And between those two types,
the organ transplant business flourishes.
All natural bodies bring a premium,
and this country's economy keeps rolling.
Only those who benefit from being in an environment in
where they are free from religious and economic constraints
can obtain high-quality cybernetic implants;
like Section 9, for example.
What's wrong?
Does your soft heart ache because you feel
like you're on the side of the exploiters?
It's not like that.
Just... I was wondering which type
of decision it was for the Major.
Checkmate!
What? That's a different game!
What are you guys doing?
Batou, you bought another piece
of body building equipment?
I don't care what you buy with your salary,
but I can't approve of your consumer habits.
What's your problem¡?
Why don't you stop pretending
to be a woman on the surface
and switch to a male cyborg body yourself?
You'll get more power that way.
Wanna fight?
Oh?
If I can take  the power
of my adversary  and use it against him,
there's no disadvantage to
having a female body, is there?
I'm expecting a good read
from the report you'll draw up
making full use of your brain "muscle".
You okay there, Batou?
Doesn't hurt at all!
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up